# Lam Oluwatobiloba Bamisebi Oluwatobiofficial 15@gmail.com

# +23408117721987

# https://github.com/Za-Genius Za Genius

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Software developer with a 2 year experience in Frontend Development and a year in Backend development. I am Passionate about the tools I use, willing to learn and add more to my arsenal to be of quality service.

I am a Quality-focused developer with a history of working well in fast-paced, challenging, and team-oriented environments.

I have experience using modern tools in building fully functional web apps and aesthetic Web pages.

#### **EDUCATION** —

# Senior secondary school

2015

Federal science and technical college, Lagos state Yaba, Nigeria.

# Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Industrial Mathematics with computer science University of Lagos, Lagos state Yaba, Nigeria.

2023

#### WORK EXPERIENCE-

### BACKEND DEVELOPER

September 2023 – October 2023

- @ HNG[x] internship
  - Assisted a small team of front-end and back-end developers with building multiple internal applications using Next is and Typescript.
  - Deployed and hosted on remote servers
  - Documented some important processes in the whole development cycle of the SASS.

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

October 2023 - June 2024

- @ GreaterEredo Nigeria @agrictrail
  - Worked with a team of developers to build multiple internal dashboard applications using Next is and Typescript.
  - API integration with graphql models
  - Documented some important processes in the whole development cycle of the SASS.

### BACKEND DEVELOPER

October 2023 – June 2024

- Worked with a small team consisting of (Mobile Developer, Product Designer, and a Product Manager)
- Job description involved building APIs for consumption on the frontend, using Nestjs and Mongodb Database.
- Documentation for API integration.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS —

- **Technologies/Skills:** JavaScript, Typescript, NodeJs, ReactJs/Nextjs, Python, Microsoft Office Suite, Google Suite, Go
- **Professional:** Problem Solving, Critical Thinking,
- Languages: English (fluent)

#### **ACTIVITIES**—

- Certificate of completion of responsive web development course by freeCodeCamp.
  - o freeCodeCamp certification